BRENDEN SCOTT

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

CONTACT



+208-970-4179



scot226@live.com



scott.it.com



linkedin.com/in/brenden-s/

EFERENCES

<u>llayton Hailey</u>

Manager of IT Madison Memorial Hospital

+208-313-0037



Ron Valleio

IT Service Desk Manager

Brigham Young University - Idaho

- **(C)** +208-550-8251
- 🔼 vallejor@byui.edu
- (in) linkedin.com/in/ronvallejo/

SKILLS

- Adept in coding:
 - Powershell
 - Python
 - SQL
 - JavaScript
- IT hardware and software troubleshooting skills
- Passionate about IT, coding and data

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

An IT professional who loves solving problems and creating automated solutions. Experienced in installing and maintaining support for software on a large scale. Proficient in coding, including Powershell, Python, SQL, and JavaScript. Let's tackle some puzzles!

WORK EXPERIENCE

<u>System Administrator - IT</u>

April 2023 - Present

Madison Memorial Hospital

- I am responsible for the mass installation of many business and clinical applications.
- · I am responsible for supporting deployed software and ensuring proper network connection and Active Directory configuration.
- · When application issues arise, I take responsibility for researching and finding solutions. Once I identify a fix, I deploy it across all the computers in the hospital.

Customer Service Operator

Sept. 2022 - April 2023

Avantgaurd Monitoring Centers

- Process alarm signals from medical devices, dispatch proper authorities, and comfort customers until help arrives.
- Enter important details about the incident into a database.
- · Notify customers' contacts about the emergency.

Shift Lead - IT Service Desk

April 2021 - Sept. 2022

Brigham Young University - Idaho

- · Supervised a team of analysts, providing coaching and guidance on their performance and ensuring proper documentation.
- · Handled inbound calls from students and faculty.
- Assisted with password resets, two-factor authentication, and operating system issues.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Brigham Young University - Idaho

- Emphasis on coding, databases, and IT.
- · Created projects in a variety of coding languages, including Python, SQL, and **Javascript**
- Took extra classes in Excel, economics, and psychology